Guide to the James Lockhart Autry Family Papers, 1832-1998 MS 003
Woodson Research Center, Rice University, Houston, Texas
- Series IV: Texas, 1875-1998, 148143
  - Allie May Autry Kelley, 1903-1998; 148156
    - Photographs - Panoramic of Rice Institute May Fete, Allie May Autry Queen, 1925; 152478 (Drawer 81)
    - Photographs - Allie May Autry Kelley - Wedding Proofs, 1930; 154132 (Box 64, Folder 5)
    - Photographs - Allie May Autry Kelley - Family, 1930-57; 154134 (Box 64, Folder 6)
    - Photographs - Allie May Autry Kelley - Family, 1960; 154547 (Box 64, Folder 7)
    - Photographs - Allie Autry Kelley and Family - Oregon, 154549 (Box 65, Folder 1-2)
    - Photographs - Allie May Autry Kelley - Friends, 1918-56; 154133 (Box 66, Folder 1)
    - Photographs - Lynn McCready, 1968; 154593 (Box 66, Folder 2)
    - Photographs - Marjorie Burkhead Milford, ca. 1926; 154594 (Box 66, Folder 3)
    - Photographs - Albert O. Singleton, 154595 (Box 66, Folder 4)
    - Photographs - U.S.S. Brush D.D. 745, n.d.; 154596 (Box 66, Folder 5)
    - Photographs - Friends, 1924-1991; 154597 (Box 66, Folder 6)
    - Photographs - #1 Remington [Houston, Texas], 154598 (Box 66, Folder 7)
    - Photographs - Unidentified, 155217 (Box 66, Folder 8)
    - Photographs - vacations, 1927, 1953, n.d.; 154135 (Box 66, Folder 9)
    - Photographs - War time garden in Houston and Oregon with family, [c. 1945]; 152485 (Box 66, Folder 10)
    - Photographs - Negatives, 155216 (Box 67, Folder 1-2)
    - Postcards, 1906-07, 1909-10; 152475 (Box 67, Folder 3)
    - Printed Materials - Entre Nous (see Oversize Materials series), 1957; 180283 (Box 67, Folder 4)
    - Printed Materials - Junior League News, October 1973; 156352 (Box 67, Folder 5)
    - Printed Materials - La Revue, December 1920; 156349 (Box 67, Folder 6)
    - Printed Materials - Ocean Times, June 27, 1954; 156351 (Box 67, Folder 7)
    - Printed Materials - The River Oaks Times, February 1, 1952 and March 29, 1957; 156353 (Box 67, Folder 8)
    - Printed Materials - The Seaside, August 1930; 156354 (Box 67, Folder 9)
    - Printed Material - Songs of the Confederacy and Plantation melodies, 156348 (Box 67, Folder 10)
    - Printed Material - Why Kinkaid School needs a gymnasium, 156165 (Box 67, Folder 11)
    - Programs - Coronation, Order of Alamo, San Antonio, Texas, 1949; 156927 (Box 67, Folder 12)
    - Programs - Fiesta Program and Invitation to the presentation of the Micajah Autry portrait to the Alamo (see Oversize Materials series), April 18, 1950; 149764 (Box 67, Folder 13)
    - Programs - General MacArthur visit to Houston, June 13, 1951; 155173 (Box 67, Folder 14)
    - Programs - Houston Buffalos, 1951; 155194 (Box 67, Folder 15)
    - Programs - Kinsloe House [Corsicana, Texas], 1962, 1988, 1993-94; 155174 (Box 67, Folder 16)
    - Programs - Miscellaneous, 155176 (Box 68, Folder 1)
    - Programs - Rice Institute May Fete, 1925; 155175 (Box 68, Folder 2)
    - Programs - Women's Finance Forum [Houston, Texas], October 1951; 154925 (Box 68, Folder 3)
    - Residence: Shadyside [Houston, TX], 152479
      - Additions and renovations, 1940-59; 153989 (Box 69, Folder 1)
      - Air-conditioning and heating, 1939-40; 153990 (Box 69, Folder 2)
      - Construction, 1938; 153991 (Box 69, Folder 3)
      - Creation of Shadyside, 1919-74; 153992 (Box 69, Folder 4)
      - [Shadyside] Directory, 154083 (Box 69, Folder 5)
      - Doors - Locks, 1938; 153993 (Box 69, Folder 6)
      - Furnishings, 1938-40; 153994 (Box 69, Folder 7)
      - Furnishings, 1940-50; 153995 (Box 69, Folder 8)
      - Furnishings, 1950-55; 153996 (Box 69, Folder 9)
      - Furnishings, 1955-66; 153997 (Box 69, Folder 10)
      - Garage, 1938; 153998 (Box 70, Folder 1)
      - General, 1938-46; 153999 (Box 70, Folder 2)
      - Landscaping, sprinklers, 1938-40; 154000 (Box 70, Folder 3)
      - Materials, 1938; 154001 (Box 70, Folder 4)
      - Nunn-McGinty Architects - Correspondence, 1938; 154002 (Box 70, Folder 5)
      - Paving, 1940; 154003 (Box 70, Folder 6)
      - Playhouse, 1938; 154004 (Box 70, Folder 7)
      - Restriction suit, 1969; 154005 (Box 70, Folder 8)
      - Restriction suit, 1969; 154006 (Box 70, Folder 9)
      - Roof, 1938-44; 154007 (Box 70, Folder 10)
      - Trustees Correspondence and Financial statements, 1934-46; 154008 (Box 70, Folder 11)
      - Utilities, 1938-76; 154009 (Box 70, Folder 12)
    - Scrapbook - Friends of Fondren Library honoring Mrs. Allie May Autry Kelley, April 4, 1992; 149768 (Box 71, Folder 1)
    - Scrapbook - Garden Scrapbook, [c. 1950-1963]; 150368 (Box 71, Folder 2)
    - Scrapbook - Oregon, [1935]; 154085 (Box 71, Folder 3)
    - Scrapbook - [pages] Wedding Guests, Christmas cards, n.d.; 155200 (Box 71, Folder 4)
  - Edward Watson Kelley, 1896-1946; 148157
    Biographical note
    Col. Edward Watson Kelley was born June 12, 1896, in Newport, Rhode Island. He was a veteran of World War I and World War II. He was awarded a Purple Heart in World War I and remained in the army until 1936 when he retired with the rank of Major. He re-entered the army in 1941 and retired from service in 1944. He married Allie May Autry in 1930. He purchased the Kelley Manufacturing Co., a steel manufacturing plant in 1936. He was active in civic, church and business affairs in Houston. He died May 1, 1946.
    - Balance Sheet, 1936-37; 155364 (Box 72, Folder 1)
    - Calling cards, n.d.; 155365 (Box 72, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence, 1941-45; 155366 (Box 72, Folder 3)
    - Estate: Auditor's report, financial accounts, September 30, 1945; 155367 (Box 72, Folder 4)
    - Estate: Auditor's report, March 31, 1949; 155368 (Box 72, Folder 5)
    - Estate: Tax return, 1946; 155369 (Box 72, Folder 6)
    - Military records - correspondence, 1936-1944; 155370 (Box 72, Folder 7)
    - Military records - orders, 1941-43; 155371 (Box 72, Folder 8)
    - Military records - pay and allowance, 1941-43; 155372 (Box 72, Folder 9)
    - Military records - promotion, 1941-42; 155373 (Box 72, Folder 10)
    - Military records - redeployment into active duty, 1941; 155374 (Box 72, Folder 11)
    - Newsclippings, 1940-46; 155375 (Box 72, Folder 12)
    - Personal expenditures, 1930; 155376 (Box 72, Folder 13)
    - Photographs, 1930-37; 152487 (Box 72, Folder 14)
    - Photographs - military, n.d.; 152486 (Box 72, Folder 15)
  - Edward Watson Kelley, Jr, 1932-; 148158
    - Certificates and Diplomas, 1940, 1954; 156410 (Box 73, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence - Mike Kelley, 1941, 1946; 156411 (Box 73, Folder 2)
    - Newsclippings, 156412 (Box 73, Folder 3)
    - Photographs - Mike Kelley, Baby, 1932-35, n.d.; 156413 (Box 73, Folder 4)
    - Photographs - Mike Kelley, n.d.; 156414 (Box 73, Folder 5)
    - Photographs - Mike Kelley + Friends, 1931-57, n.d.; 156415 (Box 73, Folder 6)
    - Photographs - Mike Kelley and Allie Kelley, 1937-39; 156416 (Box 73, Folder 7)
    - Photographs - Ellen Elizardi Kelley, wedding portrait (see Oversize Materials series), 1953-59; 156417 (Box 73, Folder 8)
    - Photographs - Mike and Ellen Kelley, wedding, 1959; 156418 (Box 73, Folder 9)
    - Photographs - Mike Kelley and family, 1973; 156419 (Box 73, Folder 10)
    - Rice Institute Commencement, June 3, 1954; 156420 (Box 73, Folder 11)
    - School transcripts and memorabilia, 1938-41; 156421 (Box 73, Folder 12)
  - Allie Autry Kelley Dittmar, 1935-1983; 148159
    - Correspondence, 1948-50; 156278 (Box 74, Folder 1)
    - Europe trip, 1956; 156279 (Box 74, Folder 2)
    - Memorabilia - ROBC (Royal Order of the Breakfast Club) certificate and banner, 1958; 156280 (Box 74, Folder 3)
    - Memorabilia - School, 1948-1950; 156281 (Box 74, Folder 4)
    - Newsclippings, 1955-59; 156282 (Box 74, Folder 5)
    - Photographs - album, 1950s; 155844 (Box 74, Folder 6)
    - Photographs - Black and White Ball, 1956; 152482 (Box 74, Folder 7)
    - Photographs - Camp, 1940s; 155836 (Box 74, Folder 8)
    - Photographs - Allie Autry Kelley, child, 155837 (Box 75, Folder 1)
    - Photographs - Christening of ship, 1940s; 155838 (Box 75, Folder 2)
    - Photographs - Debut and tea given by Allie Autry Kelley, 1958; 152483 (Box 75, Folder 3)
    - Photographs - Dittmar and Kelley family, 1962, 1975, n.d.; 149034 (Box 75, Folder 4)
    - Photographs - Europe, 1956; 152481 (Box 75, Folder 5)
    - Photographs - Fiesta Parade, 1958; 155839 (Box 75, Folder 6)
    - Photographs - High School friends, 155840 (Box 75, Folder 7)
    - Photographs - Negatives, 155863 (Box 75, Folder 8)
    - Photographs - Smith College, 155841 (Box 75, Folder 9)
    - Photographs - Allie Kelley and Joseph Dittmar wedding, 1959; 152484 (Box 76, Folder 1)
    - Photographs - Allie Kelley and Joseph Dittmar wedding, 1959; 155842 (Box 76, Folder 2)
    - Photographs - Allie Kelley and Joseph Dittmar wedding, 1959; 155843 (Box 76, Folder 3)
    - Photographs - Allie Kelley Dittmar, n.d., 149033 (Box 76, Folder 4)
    - Printed Materials - The Lamar Lancer, 1952; 156921 (Box 76, Folder 5)
    - Printed Materials - The Sophian, 1953-56; 156922 (Box 76, Folder 6)
    - Printed Materials - Shadyside Amature, n.d.; 156924 (Box 76, Folder 7)
    - Program - Edgepark Stables horse show, Houston TX, 12-29-1951; 156923 (Box 76, Folder 8)
- Series V: Oversize Materials, 180244
  - Mrs. JL Autry Household ledgers, 1927-1932; 180245 (Box 77)
  - Proclamation from Idler's Club on death of James Lockhart Autry, Jr [wrc03508], [1923]; 180246 (Box 78, Item 1)
  - Entre Nous, 1957; 180247 (Box 78, Item 2)
  - Edward W. Kelley, Jr. Scrapbook pages - McCarthy, 180248 (Box 78, Item 3)
  - Fiesta San Antonio Program [wrc04665], April 17-23, 1950; 180249 (Box 78, Item 4)
  - Texas Corinthian Yacht Club Scrapbook pages, n.d.; 180250 (Box 78, Item 5)
  - Allie Autry Kelley baby portrait, n.d.; 180251 (Box 78, Item 6)
  - Ellen Elizardi Kelley wedding portraits, 1959; 180252 (Box 78, Item 7)
  - Allie May Autry Kelley Rice Alumni appreciation, October 27, 1950; 180253 (Box 78, Item 8)
  - Houston Normal & High School Diploma-Allie May Autry, 1921; 180254 (Box 78, Item 9)
  - Houston Normal & High School Diploma-James Lockhart Autry, Jr, 1917; 180255 (Box 78, Item 10)
  - James Lockhart Autry Portrait [wrc02884], ca. 1861; 180256 (Box 79, Item 1)
  - Photograph - James Lockhart Autry III with radio equipment, 1918; 180257 (Box 79, Item 2)
  - Photograph - No. 5 Courtlandt Place, 1914; 180258 (Box 79, Item 3)
  - Photograph - Group with train, Corsicana, n.d.; 180259 (Box 79, Item 4)
  - Allie Kinsloe Kelley portraits [wrc02886], 1900; 180260 (Box 79, Item 5-6)
  - Photographs - Ralph Kinsloe, n.d.; 180261 (Box 79, Item 7)
  - Photograph - James L. Autry, Jr. as infant, ca. 1900; 180262 (Box 79, Item 8)
  - Photographs - Mike Kelley, 1953; 180263 (Box 79, Item 9)
  - Photograph - Allie Kelley Dittmar wedding portrait, 1959; 180264 (Box 79, Item 10)
  - Photograph - Dittmar and Kelley families, [1966]; 180265 (Box 79, Item 11)
  - Photographs - Allie Kelley Dittmar, n.d.; 180266 (Box 79, Item 12)
  - James L. Autry - Farms Ledger, 1901; 180267 (Box 80, Item 1)
  - Personal Financial Statements, 1914-1917; 180268 (Box 80, Item 2)
  - Matthews Garden Craft Catalog, n.d.; 180269 (Box 80, Item 3)
  - Household inventory, 1914; 180270 (Box 80, Item 4)
  - Household Ledger, 1915; 180271 (Box 80, Item 5)
  - Scrapbook - Tejas Kelley family, [1937-1940]; 180272 (Box 81, Item 1)
  - Resolution by the Board of Directors of Fidelity Trust Company of Houston [upon death of Judge Jas. L. Autry, Vice President and General Counsel], November 5, 1920; 180273 (Box 81, Item 2)
  - Scrapbook: CQ [Camp Quinibeck, Vermont], [1916]; 180274 (Box 81, Item 3)
  - Kelley Family Certificates and Diplomas, 180275 (Box 81, Item 4)
  - Inventory of Furnishings, No. 5 Courtlandt Place, 180276 (Box 81, Item 5)
  - R. C. Beale diary, Chicago, Ill., 1846-1889; 180277 (Box 82)
  - Canvass Book for the Canvass of 1855 v.s. Autry, Holly Springs, Miss., September 1855; 180278 (Box 83, Item 1)
  - Military Uniform Card Collection Album - James L. Autry, Jr, 180279 (Box 83, Item 2)
  - Scrapbook - Leather-bound memory book [high school scrapbook], [1918-1920]; 180280 (Box 84, Item 1)
  - Scrapbook - Memory Book of Schooldays [Rice Institute scrapbook], [1921]; 180281 (Box 84, Item 2)
  - Postcards, 1907-1910; 180282 (Box 85-86)
  - Photographs
    - Allie May Autry with feather boa at shoulders, colorized (Box 88)
    - Allie May Autry (2 poses, 2 images) (Box 88)
    - Allie May Autry, Rice May Fete Queen, 1925 (Box 88)
    - Bridal portrait of Mrs. Edward Watson Kelley nee Allie May Autry by Bachrach (2 poses, 4 images), 1930 (Box 88)
    - Bridal portrait of Mrs. Edward Watson Kelley nee Allie May Autry by Bachrach (3 poses, 5 images), 1930 (Box 88)
    - Bridal portrait, Allie May Autry Kelley with Anah Marie Leland Streetman and Chaille Cage (2 images), 1930 (Box 88)
    - Allie May Autry (3 poses, 3 images) [pre-wedding?], 1930 (Box 88)
    - Allie Kinsloe Autry (2 poses, 2 images) (Box 88)
    - Allie Kinsloe Autry, 1896 (Box 88)
    - Edward Watson "Mike" Kelley, Jr. collage, 1932-03-23 (Box 88)
    - Allie Autry Kelley collage, 1937-01-21 (Box 88)
    - Katherine Kelley Dittmar (Box 88)
    - ---- Kinsloe? (Box 88)
    - Mrs. W.A. Thompson, Mrs. Rodger Lapham, Mrs. George Drake, Mrs. Rufus Hardy, Miss Nan Earl Hardy, Helen Hardy Spencer (Box 88)
    - Confederate drill in Fort McRee, Penasacola [FL] harbor, 1861 (Box 89)
    - Residence of H.E. Kinsloe, Corsicana, TX [with family members] (2 images) (Box 89)
    - Camp Quinibeck campers (Allie Autry Kelley & Jessica Hobby), 1948 (Box 89)
    - Allie May Autry (3 images), 1919 (Box 89)
    - Allie May Autry (7 poses, 7 images), 1921 (Box 89)
    - Allie May Autry (2 poses, 2 images), 1920 (Box 89)
    - Allie May Autry [ #5 Courtlandt Place library] (2 poses, 2 images), 1921 (Box 89)
    - Allie May Autry (in feather boa), 1921 (Box 89)
    - Allie May Autry, 1922 (Box 89)
    - Allie May Autry, 1925? (Box 89)
    - Allie May Autry, Rice commencement (3 images), 1925 (Box 89)
    - Allie May Autry (2 poses, 2 images), 1926, 1937, or 1930 (Box 89)
    - Bridal parties (Allie May Autry serves as bridesmaid) (2 images) (Box 89)
    - Allie May Autry, 1921 (Box 89)
    - Allie May Autry Kelley [Prasilova portrait], 1930s (Box 89)
    - Allie May Autry, 1910 (Box 89)
    - Allie May Autry, 1922 (Box 89)
    - James L. Autry III (2 images), 1922 (Box 89)
    - James L. Autry III, 1917 (Box 89)
    - James L. Autry III (5 poses, 6 images) (Box 89)
    - Ralph Kinsloe (2 images) (Box 89)
    - unidentified (James L. Autry III?), 1900-05-19 (Box 89)
    - Edward Watson Kelley (3), 1937 (Box 89)
    - Ed Kelley in uniform (Box 89)
    - Billy Streetman (Box 89)
    - Edward Watson Kelley, 1943-11 (Box 89)
    - Allie May Autry (4) (Box 89)
    - Edward Watson "Mike" Kelley, Jr. (3) (Box 89)
    - Glady & Lynn McCready, 1950-10-05 (Box 89)
    - Mike Kelley, Ed Kelley, Sally Kelley, Allie Kelley, 1943 (Box 89)
    - Mrs. Khleber Atwell, Mrs. J. Lewis Thompson, Jr., Mrs. Harry McCament, Mrs. Hugh Potter, Mrs. Harold Moore, Mrs. E.W. Kelley, Mrs. Cecil Haden at Junior League luncheon (2), 1969-02-09 (Box 89)
    - Laura Haden, Helen Link, Sally Kelley, Martha Scott Moore, Debby Lester McCament, Lucille McAshan Attwell, Chaille Cage Thompson, Lucile Lester Potter at Laura Haden's daughter's debut (2), ca. 1975 (Box 89)
    - Sally Kelley group, 1980-04 (Box 89)
  - Memorabilia
    - Guest book for #1 Remington Lane, Kelley house, 1939-1954 (Box 90)
    - Edward Watson Kelley commissioning certificate as Major, United States Army, 1936-10-01 (Box 90)
    - Friends of Fondren Library Award, Rice University, to Mrs. Edward W. Kelley, 1984-11-10 (Box 90)
    - Allie May Autry [Kelley] scrapbook, 1926-1960 (Box 90)
    - Sketch for debut (Allie Autry Kelley?) dress for Sally Kelley (Box 90)
    - Plan of the campus of the University of Oregon, 1931 (Box 90)
    - Resolution by Board of Director's of St. Luke's Hospital on death of Col. Edward W. Kelley, 1946-05 (Box 90)
- Series VI: Addendum
  - Memorabilia
    - Baby book: James Lockhart Autry III, 1899 (Box 91)
    - Baby book: Katherine Kelley Dittmar, 1962 (Box 91)
    - Hymnal and Common Prayer book: Mrs. Jeanie V. Brown from [grandchildren] James L. & Allie May Autry, 1908-12-25 (Box 91)
    - Book of Common Prayer: Jeanie V. Autry, 1855 (Box 91)
    - Hymnal & Book of Common Prayer: Allie Kinsloe Autry, 1890s (Box 91)
    - Hymnal & Book of Common Prayer: James L. Autry Jr., 1890s (Box 91)
    - Speak-o-Phone recording "a snapshot of your voice", 1920s (Box 91)
    - James L. Autry Civil War travel kit, 1860s (Box 91)
    - James L. Autry Jr.: University of the South calendar, diary and cash account notebook, sunglasses in case, eyeglasses in case (2), stamp Jas L Autry Houston (Box 91)
    - James L. Autry III small notebooks (3), pen, button hook, compass (2) (Box 91)
    - Jas. L. Autry leather wallet; Mrs. Jas L. Autry leather notebook; Allie [Kinsloe Autry] calling card case with cards; J.L.A. small notebook; Mrs. Edward Watson Kelley calling cards
    - Eyeglasses with cases (12) (Box 91)
    - Passport, Allie May Autry Kelley, 1963 (Box 91)
    - Ration cards, Mrs. E.W. Kelley, Lt. Col. E.W. Kelley, 1943 (Box 91)
    - Fidelity Trust Co. business envelopes to Jas. L. Autry (Box 91)
    - Autograph book, 1932-1963 (Box 91)
    - Daily/weekly calendars (Sally Kelly & Allie Autry Kelley), 1966, 1983, 1986, 1987, 1996-97, 1997, 1953-57 (Box 91)
    - Allie Autry Kelley scrapbook, 1944 (Box 92)
    - Allie Autry Kelley scrapbook, Smith College, 1953-1954 (Box 92)
    - Allie Autry Kelley scrapbook, Allegro debut, 1957-1958 (Box 92)
    - Sally Kelley scrapbook, 90th birthday, 1993 (Box 92)
    - Allie May Autry scrapbook, 1920s (Box 92)
    - Allie Autry Kelley bride's gift book, 1959 (Box 92)
    - Allie Autry Kelley & Joe Dittmar wedding reception guest register, 1959 (Box 92)
    - Certificate: Lady Allie Autry Kelley of Houston, Texas portraying the Legend of the Rhine (Box 92)
    - Allie May Autry Kelley funeral register, 1998-06-25 (Box 92)
    - A&M College of Texas yearbook (Ralph Harris Kinsloe), 1903 (Box 92)
    - Court of the Golden Journey programs [Allie Autry Kelley], 1958-04-23 (Box 92)
    - Sally Kelley's grandchildren's commencement programs (Box 92)
    - Allie Autry Kelley Lamar High School letter (Box 92)
    - Dog Show Houston Kennel Club ribbons, 1949-04-17 (Box 92)
    - Inscriptions from books not kept (Box 92)
    - Allie Autry Kelley membership cards, certificates (Box 92)
    - Allie May Autry dance cards, calling cards, notes (Box 92)
    - Kelley Dittmar certificate, 1978-03-18 (Box 92)
    - Joseph Elmer Dittmar baptism certificate, 1944-04-08 (Box 92)
    - "Cap and Gown" yearbook of The University of the South, Sewanee, TN, 1895 (Box 92)
    - Book of Common Prayer [Jas. L. Autry, Corsicana, TX, Sept. 1887] (Box 92)
    - Book of Common Prayer with Hymnal [James L. Autry, Easter 1901] (Box 92)
    - Judge Beale early records of Navarro County, TX, 1881-1894 (Box 92)
    - Bachelor of Arts thesis, Smith College: Allie Autry Kelley, 1957-02 (Box 93)
    - A.B. thesis, Princeton University: Joseph E. Dittmar, 1954-04-19 (Box 93)
    - "...But Never this Day Come Back Again from John Brown's Body" by J. Dittmar & A.Kelley-Dittmar (Box 93)
    - "The Theory and Practice of Assmanship or The Art of Being an Absolute Plonk without Actually Intending To" by J. Dittmar & A. Kelley-Dittmar (Box 93)
  - Images
    - Judge James L. Autry, Jr. (Box 94)
    - James L. Autry, III (Box 94)
    - Allie May Autry (Box 94)
    - Autry family (Box 94)
    - Kinsloe family (Box 94)
    - Allie Autry Kelley (Box 94)
    - Allie Autry Kelley debut (Box 94)
    - Kelley family (Box 94)
    - Joseph E. Dittmar (Box 94)
    - Dittmar family (Box 94)
    - Kelley Dittmar (Box 94)
    - Jessica Hobby-Henry Catto wedding (Box 94)
    - Oregon (Box 94)
    - #1 Remington Lane, Shadyside, Houston, TX (Box 94)
    - #5 Courtlandt Place, Houston, TX (Box 94)
    - Kelleys & Dittmars (Box 94)
    - Friends (Box 94)
    - Negatives (Box 94)
    - Photograph album "My Automobile Trips" [Allie May Autry] (Box 94)
    - Photograph album [James L. Autry Jr.] (Box 94)
  - Correspondence
    - Allie Kinsloe Autry (Box 95, Folder 1)
    - Allie May Autry (Box 95, Folder 2)
    - Allie May Kelley/family (Box 95, Folder 3)
    - Mrs. Edward Kelley (Box 95, Folder 4)
    - Allie Autry Kelley (Box 95, Folder 5)
    - Allie Autry Kelley-Smith College (Box 95, Folder 6)
    - Allie Autry Kelley-Andrew Forest Muir/Rice University (Box 95, Folder 7)
    - Mike Kelley (Box 95, Folder 8)
    - Edward Dittmar (Box 95, Folder 9)
    - Michael & Diane Dittmar (Box 95, Folder 10)
    - Kelley Dittmar-Allie May Kelley (debut tea), 1986 (Box 95, Folder 11)
    - Santa-Dittmar (Box 95, Folder 12)
    - Allie May Kelley-Allie Autry Kelley
      - 1948 (Box 96, Folder 1)
      - 1949 (Box 96, Folder 2)
      - 1951 (Box 96, Folder 3)
      - 1953 (Box 96, Folder 4)
      - 1954 (Box 96, Folder 5)
      - 1955 (Box 96, Folder 6)
      - 1956 (Box 96, Folder 7)
      - 1950s (Box 96, Folder 8)
      - 1960s (Box 96, Folder 9)
    - Allie Autry Kelley, 1956 (Box 96, Folder 10)
    - Allie Autry Kelley, 1957 (Box 96, Folder 11)
    - Allie May Kelley-J.M. Roberts Jr., 1957 (Box 96, Folder 12)
    - Allie Autry Kelley, 1959 (Box 96, Folder 13)
    - Allie May Autry, 1925 (Box 96, Folder 14)
    - Allie May Autry, 1926 (Box 96, Folder 15)
    - Allie May Kelley, 1935 (Box 96, Folder 16)
    - Allie May Kelley-Kelley/Dittmar wedding, 1959 (Box 96, Folder 17)
    - Allie May Kelley-Joe Dittmar (Box 96, Folder 18)
    - Allie May Kelley-McCready (Box 96, Folder 19)
    - Allie May Kelley-friends (Box 96, Folder 20)
    - Allie May Kelley-death of Allie K. Dittmar, 1983 (Box 96, Folder 21)
    - Allie May Kelley-Garden Club (Box 96, Folder 22)
    - Allie May Kelley-grandchildren (Box 96, Folder 23)
    - Allie May Kelley-Kelley Dittmar (Box 96, Folder 24)
    - Edward Watson Kelley (Box 96, Folder 25)
    - Joe Dittmar (Box 96, Folder 26)
    - Joe Dittmar-St. Alban's (Box 97, Folder 1)
    - Joe Dittmar-Princeton, 1951 (Box 97, Folder 2)
    - Joe Dittmar-Princeton, 1952 (Box 97, Folder 3)
    - Joe Dittmar-Princeton, 1953-1954 (Box 97, Folder 4)
    - Allie Autry Kelley-Joe Dittmar (Box 97, Folder 5-7)
    - Katherine Kelley Dittmar, 1985 (Box 98, Folder 1)
    - Katherine Kelley Dittmar, 1986 (Box 98, Folder 2)
    - Katherine Kelley Dittmar, 1987 (Box 98, Folder 3)
    - Katherine Kelley Dittmar-family (Box 98, Folder 4)
    - Katherine Kelley Dittmar (Box 98, Folder 5)
    - Allie May Kelley-Allie Kelley Dittmar (Box 98, Folder 6)
  - Family events, history, residences
    - Library book inventory, #1 Remington Lane, 1950 (Box 99, Folder 1)
    - Edward Watson Kelley Collection, Rice University (Box 99, Folder 2)
    - Family invitations & announcements (Box 99, Folder 3)
    - Black & White Ball, 1957 (Box 99, Folder 4)
    - Mike Kelley-social (Box 99, Folder 5)
    - Allie Kelley-social (Box 99, Folder 6)
    - Social (Box 99, Folder 7)
    - Katherine Kelley Dittmar debut, 1986 (Box 99, Folder 8)
    - Kelley Industries (Box 99, Folder 9)
    - Allie Kinsloe Autry death, 1935 (Box 99, Folder 10)
    - Kinsloe (Box 99, Folder 11)
    - Autry House, Houston, TX (Box 99, Folder 12)
    - #5 Courtlandt Place, Houston, TX (Box 99, Folder 13)
    - Family newsclips (Box 100, Folder 1)
    - Family schooling (Box 100, Folder 2)
    - Autry Memorial Hospital School (Box 100, Folder 3)
    - Allie Autry Kelley-Fiesta de San Jacinto, 1958 (Box 100, Folder 4)
    - Kelley-Dittmar wedding, 1959 (Box 100, Folder 5)
    - Kelley-Dittmar wedding gift register, 1959 (Box 100, Folder 6)
    - Estate of James L. Autry, 1920-1921 (Box 100, Folder 7)